Guide to the Mark Bloch Postal Art Network (PAN) Archive MSS.170
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE: Series IV: Serials, 1972-2007
  - Flash Art News Supplement #146, May-June 1989 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - GET [vol. 1 no. 3], undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Girls Exclusive #14, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - High & Low, October 7, 1990-January 15, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Incredible Inquiry Catalog #6, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - The Indypendent #159, October 21-November, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Investor's Business Daily [vol. 6 no. 155], December 3, 1991 (Box Shared Fales 080, Folder 9)
  - Kaldron [no. 15, 16], Fall 1982; 1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Kaldron [#19; #20], Fall 1985; Fall 1986 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Linn's Stamp News [vol. 64 no. 3268], June 24, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Living & Loving #3, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Lo Straniero [vol. 6 no. 12; vol. 7 no. 14; vol. 8 no. 25], November 1991; November 1992; January 1993 (Folder 3 Left)
  - Lower East Side Rose [vol. 2 no. 10(49)], March 18, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Manhattan Mirror [issue 4 no. 2], June 13-July 4, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Model News [vol. 33], October 1991 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - This Month in Maine Literature [vol. 2 no. 4], April 1987 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Movement Research Performance Journal #3, Fall 1991 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Newport News, January 30, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - The New York Hangover, November 1997 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - New York Press [vol. 1 no. 6, 7], March 31, 1991; January 31, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - New York Press [vol. 2 no. 15; vol. 3 no. 2], April 14, 1989; January 12, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - New York Waste, November 1998 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - NRG [#14; #24], July 20, 1980; 1986 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Ocean Drive, April 1994; November 1994 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Pinched Nerves [vol. 2 no. 18], 1992 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Pop Culture Press #25, Fall 1992 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Profile, Spring-Summer 1986; Fall 1986 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Public Art Review [vol. 2 no. 2], Fall-Winter 1990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Request, January 1994 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Rhythm News [vol. 5 no. 4], April 1989 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Rubber Stamp Madness [vol. 3 no. 14; vol. 4 no. 19; vol. 6 no. 26, 27], March-April 1984; January-February 1985; April 1986; May-June 1986 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Serious Fun, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Slug & Lettuce #27, September-October 1992 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Soho Arts Weekly, September 25, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Sol Cultural, September 10, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - The Source [vol. 1 no. 1], Fall 1995 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - The Splatter Effect [vol. 4 no. 9], November (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Stampola [vol. 1 no. 1; vol. 2 no. 3], November 1981; November 1982 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Sunstorm, February 15-March 15, 1985; June 1985 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Sunstorm, April 1986; June 1986; Summer 1986 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Sunstorm, February-March 1987; April 1987; June-July 1987 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Sunstorm, September 1987; October 1987; 1988 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Sun Times, June 21, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Taproot Reviews #5, Summer 1994 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Test Tube [vol. 2 no. 3, 4], Summer 1981 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Tribal Call [#3; #4], 1995 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - U&lc [vol. 12 no. 1, 4], May 1985; February 1986 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - U&lc [vol. 13 no. 1, 2], May 1986; August 1986 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - U&lc [vol. 14 no. 3; vol. 15 no. 1], November 1987; February 1988 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - U&lc [vol. 15 no. 2, 3], May 1988; August 1988 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Valley Advocate, April 3, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - The Villager [vol. 72 no. 34, 35], December 11, 2002; December 18, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - The Village Voice [vol. 2 no. 1], Spring 1989 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - The Village Guide to New Music Nights, July 12-17, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - What? #6, February 1985 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Wisdom's Cry #8, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Words of the Spirit #54, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - World Art #2, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - ZuZu #5, March-April 1993 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - [Untitled French Publication], undated (Box 56, Folder 14)